http://www.4s-dawn.com/privacy-policy/

Anticoagulation
Patient Safety Monitoring – Biologic & Other High Risk Medications
4S DAWN Clinical Software Privacy Policy
At 4S DAWN Clinical Software we are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.
This policy explains when and why we collect personal information, how we use it, the conditions under which we disclose it to others and how we keep it secure.
Any questions regarding this policy can be directed by email to privacy@4s-dawn.com or in writing to 4S DAWN Clinical Software, 4 The Square, Milnthorpe, Cumbria, LA7 7QJ. Contact Name: Syd Stewart, Managing Director
Who are we?
4S DAWN Clinical Software is a division of 4S Information Systems Ltd. The company was founded in 1984 and has been involved in medical applications since start up supplying to over 300 leading healthcare organisations worldwide.
The company is registered in England and Wales, No 3165486, and the registered office is:
4S Information Systems Ltd,
4 The Square Milnthorpe, Cumbria
England
UK LA7 7QJ
How do we collect information from you?
We obtain information about you when you contact us via our website, by email or by phone, for example, when you enquire about our products and services, when you register to receive one of our newsletters or when your organisation becomes a customer of 4S DAWN Clinical Software etc.
We occasionally obtain information from publicly available sources such as NHS Trust websites in order to communicate with you.
What type of information is collected from you?
The information we collect might include your name, address, email address, area of speciality, IP address and what 4S DAWN web pages you accessed.
How is your information used?
We may use your information to:
Assist you with a sales enquiry
Process an order you have made
Support you in using our products and services
Carry out any other obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and 4S DAWN Clinical Software
Notify you of changes to our products and services
Seek your views on the products and services we provide
Send you communications that maybe of interest. These may include new products and services, company events etc.
Process a job application
Retain your services as a supplier
Your information will be held by us for as long as is necessary for the relevant activity or as long as is set out in any contract you hold with 4S DAWN Clinical Software.
Who has access to your information?
We will NOT sell or rent your information to third parties. We will NOT share your information with third parties for marketing purposes.
Your contact information will only be shared with other 4S DAWN Clinical Software customers with your explicit consent.
You are in control
You have a choice whether you wish to receive information from us or not. If you no longer wish to receive information, you can email: privacy@4s-dawn.com at any time to let us know and we will then update your details on our systems. If you unsubscribe from our newsletter using the link within the newsletter, this will only remove you from the newsletter mailing list and you may continue to receive other communication from us. If you do not wish to receive any communication from us, please specify this using the email address above.
How you can access and update your information
The accuracy of your information is important to us and if you change your email address or you are aware that any of the other information we hold about you is wrong, please email us at privacy@4s-dawn.com so that we can update our records accordingly.
Security Precautions
No sensitive data such as bank or card details are obtained and stored by us.
Non-sensitive data such as your email address that are transmitted via online and email communications can never be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you send to us and do so at your own risk. However, once we receive your information, we do our best to ensure its security within our internal systems.
Transferring your information outside Europe
For those who are located within the EU, your personal data will not be transferred outside of the EU.
If you use our products and services and you are located outside of the EU we will aim to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected as outlined in this policy.
Automated decision-making
There is nothing in place to facilitate any type of automated decision-making or profiling about you based on the personal information that we hold.
Lodging a complaint
In the first instance, please contact 4S DAWN Clinical Software at privacy@4s-dawn.com or 015395 63091 to inform us of your issue so that we are able to rectify it.
After contacting us, if you are still unhappy with the way your data has been handled by 4S DAWN Clinical Software, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority. https://ico.org.uk/concerns/
Home
Products
Anticoagulation
Rheumatology
Dermatology
Gastroenterology
Multiple Sclerosis
Heart Failure
4S Information Systems Ltd,
4 The Square Milnthorpe, Cumbria
England
UK LA7 7QJ
Registered office as above.
Registered in England & Wales No 3165486
VAT No GB 660 0737 53
International Phone: Your CountryExit Code e.g. 011 in the USA
